(Zack:)It sounds easy, but there's a lot of science
that goes into designing them.
(Howard:)Happy now? I'm moving the dirty sock.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Raj, keep an eye out for the other one.
(Penny:)-Hey, guys. This is my friend Zack.
ZACK: Hey.
(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Whoa, is that the laser? It's bitchen.
(Sheldon:)Yes. In 1917...
(Sheldon:)...when Albert Einstein established
the theoretic foundation for the laser...
(Sheldon:)...in his paper
Zur Quantentheorie der Strahlung...
(Sheldon:)...his fondest hope was that
the resultant device be "bitchen."
(Zack:)Well, mission accomplished.
(Leonard:)Let me explain what we're doing here.
(Leonard:)In 1969, the astronauts on Apollo 11...
...positioned reflectors on the moon.
We're gonna shoot a laser
off one of them...
(Leonard:)...and let the light bounce back
into this photomultiplier.
Oh, that's very cool.